{
  "id":"2.1",
  "Question":"At which layer of the OSI model does a proxy operate?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Physical",
    "B":"Network",
    "C":"Data link",
    "D":"Application"
    },
  "Answer":"B"
}
{
  "id":"2.2",
  "Question":"If a device is using node MAC addresses to funnel traffic, what layer of the OSI model is this device working in?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Layer 1",
    "B":"Layer 2",
    "C":"Layer 3",
    "D":"Layer 4"
    },
  "Answer":"B"
}
{
  "id":"2.3",
  "Question":"Which OS holds 90 percent of the desktop market and is one of our largest attack surfaces?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Windows",
    "B":"Linux",
    "C":"Mac OS",
    "D":"iOS"
    },
  "Answer":"A",
}
{
  "id":"2.4",
  "Question":"Which port uses SSL to secure web traffic?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"443",
    "B":"25",
    "C":"23",
    "D":"80"
    },
  "Answer":"A"
}
{
  "id":"2.5",
  "Question":"What kind of domain resides on a single switchport?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Windows domain",
    "B":"Broadcast domain",
    "C":"Secure domain",
    "D":"Collision domain"
    },
  "Answer":"D"
}
{
  "id":"2.6",
  "Question":"Which of the network topolgy uses a token-based access methodology?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Ethernet",
    "B":"Star",
    "C":"Bus",
    "D":"Ring"
    },
  "Answer":"C"
}
{
  "id":"2.7",
  "Question":"Hubs operate at what layer of the OSI model?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Layer 1",
    "B":"Layer 2",
    "C":"Layer 3",
    "D":"Layer 4"
    },
  "Answer":"B"
}
{
  "id":"2.8",
  "Question":"What is the proper sequence of the TCP three-way-handshake?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"SYN-ACK, ACK, ACK",
    "B":"SYN, SYN-ACK, ACK",
    "C":"SYN-SYN, SYN-ACK, SYN",
    "D":"ACK, SYN-ACK, SYN"
    },
  "Answer":""
}
{
  "id":"2.9",
  "Question":"Which of these protocols is a connection-oriented protocol?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"FTP",
    "B":"UDP",
    "C":"POP3",
    "D":"TCP"
    },
  "Answer":"D"
}
{
  "id":"2.10",
  "Question":"A scan of a network client shows that port 23 is open; what protocol is this aligned with?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Telnet",
    "B":"NetBIOS",
    "C":"DNS",
    "D":"SMTP"
    },
  "Answer":"A"
}
{
  "id":"2.11",
  "Question":"What port range is an obscure third-party application most likely to use?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"1 to 1024",
    "B":"1025 to 32767",
    "C":"32768 to 49151",
    "D":"49152 to 65535"
    },
  "Answer":"C"
}
{
  "id":"2.12",
  "Question":"Which category of firewall filters is based on packet header data only?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Stateful",
    "B":"application",
    "C":"Packet",
    "D":"Proxy"
    },
  "Answer":"C"
}
{
  "id":"2.13",
  "Question":"An administrator has just been notified of irregular network activity; what appliance functions in this manner?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"IPS",
    "B":"Stateful packet filtering",
    "C":"IDS",
    "D":"Firewall"
    },
  "Answer":"C"
}
{
  "id":"2.14",
  "Question":"Which topolgy has built-in redundancy because of its many client connections?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Token ring",
    "B":"Bus",
    "C":"Hybrid",
    "D":"Mesh"
    },
  "Answer":"D"
}
{
  "id":"2.15",
  "Question":"When scanning a network via a hardline connection to a wired-swtich NIC in promiscuous mode, what would be the extent of network traffic you expect to see?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Entire network",
    "B":"VLAN you are attached to",
    "C":"All nodes attached to the same port",
    "D":"None"
    },
  "Answer":"B"
}
{
  "id":"2.16",
  "Question":"What device acts as an intermediary between an internal client and a web source?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Router",
    "B":"PBX",
    "C":"VTC",
    "D":"Proxy"
    },
  "Answer":"A"
}
{
  "id":"2.17",
  "Question":"Which technology allows the use of a single public address to support many internal clients while also preventing exposure of internal IP address to the outside world?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"VPN",
    "B":"Tunneling",
    "C":"NTP",
    "D":"NAT"
    },
  "Answer":"D"
}
{
  "id":"2.18",
  "Question":"What network appliance sense irregularities and plays an active role in stopping that irregular activity from continuing?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"System Administrator",
    "B":"Firewall",
    "C":"IPS",
    "D":"IDP"
    },
  "Answer":"C"
}
{
  "id":"2.19",
  "Question":"You have the option in your IDS to notify you via e-mail if it senses any network irregularities. Checking the logs, you notice a few incidents but you did not recieve any alerts. What protocol needs to be configuredon the IDS?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"NTP",
    "B":"SNMP",
    "C":"POP3",
    "D":"SMTP"
    },
  "Answer":"D"
}
{
  "id":"2.20",
  "Question":"Choosing a protective network appliance, you want a device that will inspect packets at the most granular level possible while provideing improved traffic efficiency. What appliance would satisfy these requirements?",
  "Choices":{
    "A":"Layer 3 switch",
    "B":"NAT-enabled router",
    "C":"Proxy firewall",
    "D":"Packet filtering firewall"
    },
  "Answer":"D"
}
